Guide to the Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, Records SC0117
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 1990-189
  - Education Abroad Program (EAP) 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - English for International Business People 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Recruiting Drive 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs (NAFSA) 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Orientation Meetings 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Raychem Internship 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Washington Internship 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Italy: Florence Course Abstracts 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Italy: Florence Course Proposals 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Florence Directed Reading 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Florence Curriculum 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Florence Program Evaluations 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Course Evaluations 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Italy: Florence McConnell Course Abstract (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - France: Paris Program Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Course Evaluations 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - France: Tours Registration Holds 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - France: Paris Enrollments/Withdrawals 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Curricula General 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Memoranda and Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Staff Meeting Minutes 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Florence Curriculum 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - France: Tours Curriculum 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - France: Tours Student Orientation Handbook (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - France: Paris Student Orientation Handbook (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Spain: Salamanca Student Orientation Handbook (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - France: Paris Orientation 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - France: Paris Course Proposals 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - France: Paris Course Proposals 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - France: Paris Curriculum 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - France: Paris Curriculum 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - France: Paris Curriculum 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - France: Paris Library List 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - France: Paris Housing 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - France: Paris Administration 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - France: Paris Publicity, Including Photographs (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - France: Paris Applications/Selection 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - France: Paris Orientation Travel 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - France: Paris Program Evaluation Forms 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - France: Tours Course Abstracts 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - France: Tours Course Proposals 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - France: Tours Course Proposals 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - France: Tours Curriculum 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - France: Tours Enrollment/Withdrawals 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Course Evaluations 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - France: Tours Alumni Association 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - France: Tours Calendar/Schedules 1977-1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - France: Tours Administration 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - France: Tours Student Concerns 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - France: Tours Orientation 1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - France: Tours Orientation Travel 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Additional Material, Accession 1994-076
  - Committee on General Studies - Subcommittee on Overseas Campuses Minutes 4/1968-6/1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CFSP (Committee on Foreign Study Programs) Minutes 1/1970-6/1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CFSP Minutes 10/1971-5/1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CFSP Minutes 10/1972-5/1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Italy: Florence Flood Correspondence, Magazine, Newspaper, Article, Photographs, Negatives 11/1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Italy Miscellaneous Publications (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CFSP/Overseas Program Miscellaneous 1967-1988 (bulk 1974) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Director's Conference Agendas 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Commission on Overseas Campuses and Merryman Visits 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CFSP Reports, Memoranda, Etc. 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Britain: Cliveden Housing 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession 1999-014
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: KCJS Program Agreements (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Japan Stanford Association-member lists (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Program Proposals (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Hara Meeting (9/86) re. Okada Industrial Park (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Forum-Overseas Studies-agreement (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Stanford V.I.P. Visits to Japan (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information: Kansai Science City (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Reference Information (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Correspondence: Kennedy Thank-You Letters (1986) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Correspondence: Tokyo Lunch with Kennedy (Nov. 28, 1986) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Correspondence: Christmas Card List (1986) -also MEISHI (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Correspondence: Nancy and Dan Okimoto-records of notes to (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Japan Center: (Label In Japanese) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Full Packet of Letters, Etc. sent on 3/3/87 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Kyoto University Relationship (Michida et al) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Publicity: Kyoto Center Descriptions (English) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Publicity: Kyoto Center Descriptions (Japanese) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Publicity: Newspaper Articles-Stanford (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Publicity: "Objectives" Statement (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Japan Center-Fundraising: part 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Japan Center-Fundraising: part 2 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Japan Center-Opening (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Negotiations-Tazuke (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Negotiations-City of Kyoto (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Osaka Gas (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Land Site (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Land Site-Photos (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Building: Obayashi Plans (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1987 November-December (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1988 January-February (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1988 March-April (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1988 May (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1988 December (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1989 January (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1989 February (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1989 March-April (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Stanford Japan Center: Overseas Studies Chron File: 1989 May-July (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Additional Material, Accession 2009-224
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, general correspondence, 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Nov. 1994 meeting: memos, reports, notes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Jan. 1995 meeting: memo, report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, March 1995 meeting: memo, notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, April 1995 meeting: memo, notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, May 1995 meeting: memo, notes (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, general correspondence, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Oct. 1995 meeting: memo, miscellaneous material, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Nov. 1995 meeting: Review of Stanford in Paris, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Paris Subcommittee: memo, reports, email, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Feb. 1996 meeting: Review of Kyoto-SCTI program and notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Kyoto Subcommittee: memo and report 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, faculty applications, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, May 1996 meeting: Review of Stanford Program in Oxford 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Oxford Subcommittee: memo, reports, email, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, general correspondence 1996-97 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Moscow Review: report, memos, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, faculty appointments 1996-97 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Santiago Review: memo, report, email 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, May 1997 meeting: memo, reports 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, October 1997 meeting: memo, notes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Feb. 1998 meeting: notes 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, March 1998 meeting: memo 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, general correspondence, 1997-98 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Florence Subcommittee: review 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, general correspondence [contains only committee list and charge] 1998-99 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, October 1998 meeting: notes, email, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Feb. 1999 meeting: Review of Kyoto SCTI Program, and notes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, May 1999 meeting: memo, report, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Nov. 1999 meeting: memos 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, Feb. 2000 meeting: roster, correspondence, newsletters, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Overseas Studies Advisory Committee, May 2000 meeting: memos, reports, newsletters (all re program in Puebla, Mexico) 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Panels: Berlin, Florence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Panels: Moscow, Oxford, Paris, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Panels: Japan, Latin America, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Panels 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Overseas Study Program 2000-2005 (bound book of images produced through Shutterfly) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Celebrating 25 Years in Oxford (photo brochure) 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stanford-in-Oxford [poem] by Robert Siegel, May 91-6, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Overseas Studies at Forty; a production of The Stanford Channel, September 1998 [VHS cassette] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Gelpi, Tom Hare, and Gil Masters / Teaching Overseas Feb. 3, 1999; Facilitator - Lucia Hammar [VHS cassette] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Kyoto Center for Japanese Studies, copyright 2000 [VHS cassette] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Japanese TV clips of Stanford Japan Center Opening [VHS cassette] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Behind the Red Door [about the Oxford Program] - Master Copy 18 min.; for Stanford University Overseas Studies Program by Jason Wishnow with Miguel Drayton and Alder Yarrow ca. 1995 [Umatic cassette] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Behind the Red Door [VHS cassette] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, Accession 2010-071
  - France, probably Tours: photographs, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs, March 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: Stanford News Service contact sheets, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: Stanford News Service prints, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: 35mm contact prints 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs (villa) 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs of faculty (ID type) early 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs (students in the Villa) circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: 35mm negatives, 1980s-90s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs (color prints) 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: photographs of the Villa and faculty apartment, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: 30th Anniversary reception (at SU) Feb. 23, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs of class groups I-XXXI (some missing) 1958-73 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs (digital) of group XVI 1961 and their 2008 reunion (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographic negative, aerial view, of Landget Burg (site of Stanford in Germany 1958-74) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs of students meeting with mayor, 1960s-70s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: color slides 1966 and undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs of house at Beutelsbach, 1960s or 1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: Stanford News Service photographs, late 1960s-early 1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: Stanford News Service contact prints, early 1970s; includes some from Vienna (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: 35mm negatives and contact prints, early 1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs at Landget Burg, including Richard Lyman, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Beutelsbach: photographs March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Bonn: Stanford News Service contact prints, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Bonn: Stanford News Service photographs, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Hamburg: photographs mid-1960s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Hamburg: photographs, April-Sept. 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: index to slides (used in student orientation) 2000- on (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: slides 2000 on (1 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: slides 2000 on (2 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: slides 2000 on (3 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: slides 2000 on (4 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Berlin: slides 2000 on (5 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Beat Cal photo at stadium in Budapest, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Oversize photograph: Stanford in Germany, Beutelsbach Group XVI, 1966 (Folder 1)
- Additional Material, Accession 2010-099
  - China Beijing program 5th Anniversary video, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
  - China Beijing program photographs: students and events 2004 Fall - 2010 Spring [computer disc with list] (Box 1)
  - Cooperaton and Communication, PKU school magazine (in Chinese) 2008; pp. 20-27 on Stanford program (Box 1)
  - China Beijing program handbooks, 2004-2010 (Box 1)
  - Calendar made for 5th Anniversary of China Beijing program, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: packet for celebration, June 20-22, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: special issue of The Tuscan Scene, Spring/Summer 2010 (Box 2)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: menu for the reunion dinner hosted by Peter and Helen Bing (Box 2)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: photographs, 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: commemorative coin in case (Box 2)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: 50th Anniversary Celebration, Welcome Dinner reception, June 20, 2010; 2.1U; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: 50th Anniversary Celebration, Salone dei Cinquecento, Palazzo Vecchio, June 21, 2010; 2.2U; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd)
  - Florence Program 50th Anniversary: 50th Anniversary Celebration, Aula Magna, Universita di Firenze, June 22, 2010; 2.3U; 2 optical disc(s) (dvd)
- Additional Material: Historical materials and publications, 1962-2002; Accession 2010-138; 1 Linear Feet
  - OSP general history, 1982-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Australia: history, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beijing: history (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Berlin (also Beutelsbach): history, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Buenos Aires: history, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Florence: history (includes photographs), 1969-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jerusaleum: history, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Krakow: history, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kyoto: history, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Moscow: history, 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Oxford (also Harlaxton, Cliveden): history (includes photographs and "The Clues: Getting on at Oxford"), 1978-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Paris (also Tours): history (includes photographs), 1966-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Puebla: history, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Salamanca: history (only photographs) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Salamanca Program; courses taught, summarized by Stanford students, 1988-1990 and undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Santiago: history, 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Vienna: history, 1969-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Yearbooks by students: programs in France, Germany and Italy, 1966-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stanford in France Group VII Bios and Memories Reunion, 2002 Oct. 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Club Italia Directory, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Krupp Internship Program for Stanford Students in Germany (booklet in German), circa 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Program brochures, 1962-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Studies Bulletins (description of programs and classes), 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Additional Material: Historical materials and photographs, 1958-2009; Accession 2011-058; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Beutelsbach history, miscellaneous items, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Naimark, Norman "Stanford Overseas Studies: Then and Now" article and notes, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Naimark, sources for article: photocopied letter, memos, reports, clippings, etc. (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Naimark, sources for article: possibly original reports, notes, correspondence, 1991-2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Naimark, sources for article: Richard M. Berthold "err Wachtmeister, Wo Ist der Dom? Stray Notes from the Periphery of German Studies", undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kramer, Karen: photocopied documents on early history of the Berlin center (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kramer, Karen: photocopied documents on general overseas program history (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, England, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Europe, 1958-circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Latin America, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Additional Material: Slides by Douglas Cameron of Stanford-in-England, 1984-1985; Accession 2011-063; 98 slide(s)
  - Slides of students, dormitories, and some excursions, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Additional Material: 50th Anniversary Celebration, 2010 Jun 20-22; Accession 2011-531
  - Aula Magna, Universita' di Firenze, 2010 Jun 22; 2 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1U, Box 2U)
  - Welcome dinner reception hosted by Helen and Peter Bing, 2010 Jun 20; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3U)
- Additional Material: Student Letters, 2007-2013; Accession 2013-083
  - Berlin: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cape Town: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cape Town: Spring Quarter 2009-2010, 1 folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Florence: Fall Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Florence: Spring Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Madrid: Fall Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Madrid: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Moscow: Fall Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Paris: Fall Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Paris: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Paris: Spring Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Oxford: Spring Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Santiago: Winter Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Santiago: Spring Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Beijing: Spring Quarter 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kyoto: Fall Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Florence: Fall Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Oxford: Spring Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Paris: Winter Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Santiago: Winter Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Santiago: Spring Quarter 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beijing: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Berlin: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Berlin: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Berlin: Spring Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Florence: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Florence: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Florence: Spring Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Kyoto: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Madrid: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Madrid: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Madrid: Spring Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Moscow: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Oxford: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Paris: Fall Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Paris: Winter Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Paris: Spring Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Santiago: Fall 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Santiago: Spring Quarter 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Beijing: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Beijing: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Berlin: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Florence: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cape Town: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cape Town: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kyoto: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Madrid: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Madrid: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Madrid: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Florence: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Berlin: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Berlin: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Oxford: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Oxford: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Oxford: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Paris: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Paris: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Paris: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Santiago: Fall Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Santiago: Winter Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Santiago: Spring Quarter 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Berlin: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Berlin: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Berlin: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Beijing: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Beijing: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cape Town: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cape Town: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Florence: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Florence: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Madrid: Fall Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Madrid: Winter Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Madrid: Spring Quarter 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 53)